I got a new outfit from Essentino.pl. This jacket and in this box, which I can't show you yet because I only have one arm left, is a leggings and a tube top. It's made of latex and I'm going to try it on with you together because I haven't done it yet.
the top and the leggings. Oh I just noticed it's inside out. Shiny on the inside.
Now let's add some heels.
Oops now I'm too tall for the frame.
Let's change that.
Okay I added some boots.
I'm not used to this kind of top. I don't think I've ever worn a tube top before.
So that is kind of cool to see. I think I can wear it. Maybe something's missing at the neck now.
How about a necklace or choker? Like this? Yeah, I think that's okay.
And since this is not suited for anything else than hot summer,
I have a jacket as well. Or let me show you the pants from behind first.
It has shoulder pads.
Let's see how that'll look.
Okay, it's kind of biker style and the arms are really long but I think it's a bit too
loose to wear open so let's try and close it.
Yeah, I think that's better.
It's a bit of biker style.
The shoulder pads are not bad.
I like them.
Cool, that's nice.
It does look like latex from the outside but as you've seen I've got into it really fast
and not just because of the special effects.
It's because it's not latex on the inside but fabric.
And one last idea going full into the Bad F-Bird styling.
also a cool idea just add multiple belts and whatever you have laying around at home.
Okay one last time without the jacket because I want to see that top again.
So that's my look.